We're going to apply a toner to take off any excess product and we're going to go ahead and apply the mask.
We're going to start with the eye pads because we want to protect the eyes.
And we're once again going to use a hydrating mask.
So we're going to go ahead and apply the mask in light strokes.
It's a lovely shade of green, very smooth, has a lot of nice aroma to it, and once again, very hydrating.
We're going to put this mask on and allow it to sit about five minutes.
And then we will return, remove the mask and add the final touches which will be a hydrating creme.
And this, this mask is a hydrating mask and one of the components that is very hydrating is a shay butter and that is one of the very highly hydrating masks that we have here.
And for this type of skin this is what you want to use.
If you are a client who had very oily skin or little bit oiler skin you would not want to use this mask.
We have several selections of different masks for different types of skins.
So we will let this mask sit for five minutes and then we will move forward.
Okay.